1490305398259,-360,'{"status": "COMPLETED", "start_timestamp": 1490305168852, "name": "MoodSurfing", "trigger_type": "USER", "question_answers": [{"exercise_type": "Use Your Imagination", "status": "COMPLETED", "start_time": 1490305206988, "end_time": 1490305272405, "questions": [{"completion_time": 1490305212711, "response": null, "question_text": "This exercise can help you manage unpleasant thoughts or emotions by using your imagination.\n\nYou can press the [speaker icon] on any screen to have the instructions read to you.", "prompt_time": 1490305222931, "question_id": 0}, {"question_text": "We all experience unpleasant thoughts or emotions from time to time. Sometimes it is possible to change them, and sometimes it\u2019s not.\n\n\nHave you ever noticed that sometimes trying to get rid of a thought or an emotion actually makes it stronger?\n", "response_option": ["Yes", "No"], "prompt_time": 1490305226929, "completion_time": 1490305222891, "question_type": "multiple_choice", "response": ["Yes"], "question_id": 1}, {"question_text": "So try not to fight them or change the way you feel. Here is an exercise that can be used instead.", "prompt_time": 1490305226882, "completion_time": 1490305226841, "response": null, "condition": ["1:Yes"], "question_id": 2}, {"question_text": "People manage unpleasant thoughts or emotions in various ways. The following is a useful exercise that can help people notice how they feel when they are stressed without trying to change it or make it go away.", "prompt_time": 1490305240318, "completion_time": 0, "response": null, "condition": ["1:No"], "question_id": 3}, {"completion_time": 1490305240188, "response": null, "question_text": "Take a moment and try to visualize a thought or an emotion that you are currently having as a tangible object.\n\nImagine it placed on a table before you. Look at it for a couple of seconds.\n\nWhat does it look like?\n\n Continue observing it and answer the following questions:", "prompt_time": 1490305250421, "question_id": 4}, {"question_text": "Is it...\n", "prompt_time": 1490305259089, "completion_time": 1490305250326, "question_type": "multiple_select_special", "response": ["Small", "Rough", "Hard", "Heavy"], "question_id": 5}, {"question_text": "What color is it?\n", "prompt_time": 1490305261680, "completion_time": 1490305258914, "question_type": "color", "response": ["434343"], "question_id": 6}, {"question_text": "Does it have a shape?\n", "response_option": ["Yes", "No", "NA"], "prompt_time": 1490305265663, "completion_time": 1490305261577, "question_type": "multiple_choice", "response": ["Yes"], "question_id": 7}, {"completion_time": 1490305265602, "response": null, "question_text": "Continue observing and studying your object for another minute or so. \n\nFocusing on the details and trying to describe them can help you distance yourself from negative thoughts or emotions.\n\nYou can use this strategy at anytime to accept the existence of your negative thoughts or feelings and distance yourself from them.", "prompt_time": 1490305271678, "question_id": 8}, {"question_text": "Do you think that this exercise can be useful in dealing with you stress?\n", "response_option": ["Yes", "No"], "prompt_time": 1490305271633, "completion_time": 1490305271628, "question_type": "multiple_choice", "response": ["Yes"], "question_id": 9}, {"completion_time": 0, "response": null, "question_text": "Congratulations.\n\n You have finished \"Use your Imagination\" Exercise", "prompt_time": 1490305271638, "question_id": 10}]}, {"exercise_type": "Notice and Accept", "status": "COMPLETED", "start_time": 1490305287065, "end_time": 1490305337406, "questions": [{"completion_time": 1490305298970, "response": null, "question_text": "This exercise can help you become more aware of and accept any physical sensations caused by stress.\n\nYou can press the [speaker icon] on any screen to have the instructions read to you.", "prompt_time": 1490305302206, "question_id": 0}, {"question_text": "Sometimes, you may experience stress physically. Try taking a moment to just notice what is happening to your body.", "response_option": ["body"], "prompt_time": 1490305306019, "completion_time": 1490305302155, "question_type": "image", "response": null, "question_id": 1}, {"question_text": "Are you experiencing any ... (select all that apply)", "response_option": ["Tension", "Shakiness", "Pain", "Cigarette craving", "Restlessness", "Irritability", "Other physical sensations", "None of the above"], "prompt_time": 1490305305974, "completion_time": 1490305305934, "question_type": "multiple_select", "response": ["Cigarette craving"], "question_id": 2}, {"question_text": "Different people experience stress in different ways; for some people the physical manifestations of stress can be as unpleasant as their stressful thoughts.  \n\nNext time you experience any of these physical sensations, come back to this exercise and try it out.", "prompt_time": 1490305309993, "completion_time": 0, "response": null, "condition": ["2:None of the above"], "question_id": 3}, {"question_text": "Take a couple minutes and try to focus on your _____\n\nRemember, these are just sensations, even though your mind may label them as ''good'' or ''bad''; you can simply allow them to be present, notice them and accept them for what they are, without judgement.\n\n\nTake a moment to answer the following questions about your _____", "prompt_time": 1490305315603, "completion_time": 1490305309831, "response": null, "condition": ["2:Tension", "2:Shakiness", "2:Pain", "2:Cigarette craving", "2:Restlessness", "2:Irritability", "2:Other physical sensations"], "question_id": 4}, {"question_text": "Is your _____ in one place or in multiple places in your body?\n", "response_option": ["One", "Multiple"], "response": ["Multiple"], "completion_time": 1490305315528, "question_type": "multiple_choice", "prompt_time": 1490305320610, "condition": ["2:Tension", "2:Shakiness", "2:Pain", "2:Cigarette craving", "2:Restlessness", "2:Irritability", "2:Other physical sensations"], "question_id": 5}, {"question_text": "Is it changing or does it always stay the same?", "response_option": ["Changing", "Always the Same"], "response": ["Changing"], "completion_time": 1490305320459, "question_type": "multiple_choice", "prompt_time": 1490305322123, "condition": ["2:Tension", "2:Shakiness", "2:Pain", "2:Cigarette craving", "2:Restlessness", "2:Irritability", "2:Other physical sensations"], "question_id": 6}, {"question_text": "Is it strong or weak?", "response_option": ["Strong", "Weak"], "response": ["Strong"], "completion_time": 1490305322023, "question_type": "multiple_choice", "prompt_time": 1490305333881, "condition": ["2:Tension", "2:Shakiness", "2:Pain", "2:Cigarette craving", "2:Restlessness", "2:Irritability", "2:Other physical sensations"], "question_id": 7}, {"question_text": "Are there any places in your body where you don''t feel it?", "response_option": ["Yes", "No"], "response": ["No"], "completion_time": 1490305333789, "question_type": "multiple_choice", "prompt_time": 1490305335083, "condition": ["2:Tension", "2:Shakiness", "2:Pain", "2:Cigarette craving", "2:Restlessness", "2:Irritability", "2:Other physical sensations"], "question_id": 8}, {"question_text": "Physical sensations are an important part of how we experience stress. The acceptance of those sensations can help us deal with that stress in a healthy way.", "prompt_time": 1490305336781, "completion_time": 1490305334983, "response": null, "condition": ["2:Tension", "2:Shakiness", "2:Pain", "2:Cigarette craving", "2:Restlessness", "2:Irritability", "2:Other physical sensations"], "question_id": 9}, {"question_text": "Did you find this exercise useful in dealing with your stress?", "response_option": ["Yes", "No"], "response": ["Yes"], "completion_time": 1490305336736, "question_type": "multiple_choice", "prompt_time": 1490305336784, "condition": ["2:Tension", "2:Shakiness", "2:Pain", "2:Cigarette craving", "2:Restlessness", "2:Irritability", "2:Other physical sensations"], "question_id": 10}, {"completion_time": 0, "response": null, "question_text": "Congratulations.\n\n You have finished \"Notice and Accept\" Exercise", "prompt_time": 1490305336742, "question_id": 11}]}, {"exercise_type": "Surf the Mood", "status": "COMPLETED", "start_time": 1490305369756, "end_time": 1490305389761, "questions": [{"question_text": "This exercise can help you use guided imagery to manage stress.\n\nAre you currently experiencing any unpleasant emotions?", "response_option": ["Yes", "No"], "prompt_time": 1490305369772, "completion_time": 1490305352598, "question_type": "multiple_choice", "response": ["Yes"], "question_id": 0}, {"question_text": "Video page", "response_option": ["peak"], "response": null, "completion_time": 1490305369019, "question_type": "video", "prompt_time": 1490305369781, "condition": ["0:Yes"], "question_id": 1}, {"question_text": "Sometimes unpleasant emotions can become very intense and seem somewhat overpowering. \n\nIf this happens, you can imagine these emotions as a wave. Let me guide you through this exercise.", "prompt_time": 1490305369779, "completion_time": 0, "response": null, "condition": ["0:No"], "question_id": 2}, {"question_text": "Begin by relaxing and just focusing on the presence of your emotions. Do not pass judgment; just acknowledge them.\n\n\nImagine your unpleasant emotions as a wave, rising, peaking, and then fading away.", "prompt_time": -1, "completion_time": 0, "response": null, "condition": ["0:No"], "question_id": 3}, {"question_text": "Imagine yourself riding that wave. Simply be aware of the movement as it washes through you.\n\nBe aware of the sensations without reacting.", "response_option": ["react"], "response": null, "completion_time": 0, "question_type": "image", "prompt_time": -1, "condition": ["0:No"], "question_id": 4}, {"question_text": "Continue being aware of your emotions as they ebb and flow like waves.\n\nImagine yourself riding those waves, being present and not reacting as they peak and then fade.", "response_option": ["peak"], "response": null, "completion_time": 0, "question_type": "image", "prompt_time": 1490305389113, "condition": ["0:No"], "question_id": 5}, {"question_text": "Do you think this exercise can be useful in dealing with your unpleasant emotions?", "response_option": ["Yes", "No"], "prompt_time": 1490305389118, "completion_time": 1490305389070, "question_type": "multiple_choice", "response": ["No"], "question_id": 6}, {"completion_time": 0, "response": null, "question_text": "Congratulations.\n\n You have finished \"Surf the Mood\" Exercise. You can come back to this exercise and surf your mood whenever you experience negative emotions.", "prompt_time": 1490305389116, "question_id": 7}]}], "id": "MOODSURFING", "end_timestamp": 1490305398252}'
1490402703827,-360,'{"status": "MISSED", "start_timestamp": 1490402703802, "name": "MoodSurfing", "trigger_type": "SYSTEM", "id": "MOODSURFING", "end_timestamp": 1490402703802}'
1490477769071,-360,'{"status": "COMPLETED", "start_timestamp": 1490477721096, "name": "MoodSurfing", "trigger_type": "USER", "question_answers": [{"exercise_type": "Notice and Accept", "status": "COMPLETED", "start_time": 1490477723877, "end_time": 1490477765684, "questions": [{"completion_time": 1490477727295, "response": null, "question_text": "This exercise can help you become more aware of and accept any physical sensations caused by stress.\n\nYou can press the [speaker icon] on any screen to have the instructions read to you.", "prompt_time": 1490477729784, "question_id": 0}, {"question_text": "Sometimes, you may experience stress physically. Try taking a moment to just notice what is happening to your body.", "response_option": ["body"], "prompt_time": 1490477737487, "completion_time": 1490477729741, "question_type": "image", "response": null, "question_id": 1}, {"question_text": "Are you experiencing any ... (select all that apply)", "response_option": ["Tension", "Shakiness", "Pain", "Cigarette craving", "Restlessness", "Irritability", "Other physical sensations", "None of the above"], "prompt_time": 1490477737441, "completion_time": 1490477737383, "question_type": "multiple_select", "response": ["Cigarette craving", "Restlessness", "Tension"], "question_id": 2}, {"question_text": "Different people experience stress in different ways; for some people the physical manifestations of stress can be as unpleasant as their stressful thoughts.  \n\nNext time you experience any of these physical sensations, come back to this exercise and try it out.", "prompt_time": 1490477747571, "completion_time": 0, "response": null, "condition": ["2:None of the above"], "question_id": 3}, {"question_text": "Take a couple minutes and try to focus on your _____\n\nRemember, these are just sensations, even though your mind may label them as ''good'' or ''bad''; you can simply allow them to be present, notice them and accept them for what they are, without judgement.\n\n\nTake a moment to answer the following questions about your _____", "prompt_time": 1490477754044, "completion_time": 1490477747405, "response": null, "condition": ["2:Tension", "2:Shakiness", "2:Pain", "2:Cigarette craving", "2:Restlessness", "2:Irritability", "2:Other physical sensations"], "question_id": 4}, {"question_text": "Is your _____ in one place or in multiple places in your body?\n", "response_option": ["One", "Multiple"], "response": ["Multiple"], "completion_time": 1490477753945, "question_type": "multiple_choice", "prompt_time": 1490477756978, "condition": ["2:Tension", "2:Shakiness", "2:Pain", "2:Cigarette craving", "2:Restlessness", "2:Irritability", "2:Other physical sensations"], "question_id": 5}, {"question_text": "Is it changing or does it always stay the same?", "response_option": ["Changing", "Always the Same"], "response": ["Always the Same"], "completion_time": 1490477756829, "question_type": "multiple_choice", "prompt_time": 1490477759454, "condition": ["2:Tension", "2:Shakiness", "2:Pain", "2:Cigarette craving", "2:Restlessness", "2:Irritability", "2:Other physical sensations"], "question_id": 6}, {"question_text": "Is it strong or weak?", "response_option": ["Strong", "Weak"], "response": ["Weak"], "completion_time": 1490477759318, "question_type": "multiple_choice", "prompt_time": 1490477761770, "condition": ["2:Tension", "2:Shakiness", "2:Pain", "2:Cigarette craving", "2:Restlessness", "2:Irritability", "2:Other physical sensations"], "question_id": 7}, {"question_text": "Are there any places in your body where you don''t feel it?", "response_option": ["Yes", "No"], "response": ["Yes"], "completion_time": 1490477761670, "question_type": "multiple_choice", "prompt_time": 1490477763079, "condition": ["2:Tension", "2:Shakiness", "2:Pain", "2:Cigarette craving", "2:Restlessness", "2:Irritability", "2:Other physical sensations"], "question_id": 8}, {"question_text": "Physical sensations are an important part of how we experience stress. The acceptance of those sensations can help us deal with that stress in a healthy way.", "prompt_time": 1490477765009, "completion_time": 1490477762980, "response": null, "condition": ["2:Tension", "2:Shakiness", "2:Pain", "2:Cigarette craving", "2:Restlessness", "2:Irritability", "2:Other physical sensations"], "question_id": 9}, {"question_text": "Did you find this exercise useful in dealing with your stress?", "response_option": ["Yes", "No"], "response": ["Yes"], "completion_time": 1490477764961, "question_type": "multiple_choice", "prompt_time": 1490477765013, "condition": ["2:Tension", "2:Shakiness", "2:Pain", "2:Cigarette craving", "2:Restlessness", "2:Irritability", "2:Other physical sensations"], "question_id": 10}, {"completion_time": 0, "response": null, "question_text": "Congratulations.\n\n You have finished \"Notice and Accept\" Exercise", "prompt_time": 1490477764967, "question_id": 11}]}], "id": "MOODSURFING", "end_timestamp": 1490477769060}'
1490561044940,-360,'{"status": "MISSED", "start_timestamp": 1490561044905, "name": "MoodSurfing", "trigger_type": "SYSTEM", "id": "MOODSURFING", "end_timestamp": 1490561044905}'
1490753102515,-360,'{"status": "MISSED", "start_timestamp": 1490753102494, "name": "MoodSurfing", "trigger_type": "SYSTEM", "id": "MOODSURFING", "end_timestamp": 1490753102494}'
